Hello Gas, welcome to my YouTube
channel named Sony Tax John. Today
's video will be on health policy. There are
many policies available in the market like
health policy and
term policy. So, everyone can choose
whichever policy they want to buy, but I
just want to tell you one thing that my
experience related to health policy,
I am sharing that with you through this video.
Some of my collectors had
policies through agents, some collectors are
dealing directly with the company, that is, they do business
directly with the company
through online, so I have Akshay Tapa,
then S Chola Mandalam and ICC Lombard. I have a
very good experience with these three companies. Whatever claim
I have filed has been
executed properly and
I have also received the claim. The maximum I have done is for Rs 50,000. It has ranged from Rs
10,000 to Rs 50,000.
Whatever bill I have filed has been
executed properly and I have received
its payment within 4 days.
So both of these pimples in my account are
such that after completing the process, there is an
incomplete process in it, then they
start telling that the process is not good etc. or the company is not good, so the
process is not like that, if you do the accident in a proper way,
definitely whatever money
you have spent
in the beginning, it gets credited to your account through reimbursement,
but if you do the process and through a right way
or if
you get the right direction or if you get the right guidance,
definitely you
receive the bill or hard on money, so whenever
you buy a health policy through any agent,
see if the agent is
helping you well, then well and good, or
you can buy it through the company's website,
so the middle of this video was
that whatever policy you are buying, do it in a proper
way, lastly 2 years ago I had
uploaded a video on which a lot of
comments were coming, so recently I have made a
claim of Rs 26000, this claim is
within 2  I have received a mail that will be created within a few days.
I will share a proof of it with you through this video.
If you like this video,
please like it and if you have any other video, please
give it to me in your comment through this video so that I can revert it for you.